This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hat crew,
Luffy is headed to Navy Headquarters to rescue his brother Ace from execution.
Three hours remain.
The Navy has gathered every possible force at Marineford
in anticipation of an attack by the Whitebeard Pirates.
Ace, I would like you to tell them the name of your father.
The name of my father is Whitebeard.
Not true!
And your mother's name?
Fort Gus D. Rouge.
And thus, a year and three months after the death of his father,
a child was born with the blood of the world's most odious villain in his veins.
That child was you!
Your true father is Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates!
Then it survived!
His bloodline...
Roger's bloodline lives!
A vast fleet appears!
Here come the Whitebeard Pirates!
That monster had a kid? I can't believe it!
That means the legend of Gold Roger? It never ended!
Why haven't they killed him already?
If he's the son of the King of the Pirates, then he's too dangerous to live!
If only I'd caught him and put him up for auction!
I could've made a fortune!
So many twists! A fine execution!
Does that mean he got his Firefist powers from his father?
Better yet, you think he's got the One Piece?
What's it matter? He's as good as dead!
That bloodline's about to get wiped off the face of the planet!
So, Ace isn't Luffy's real brother after all?
Gold Roger? He's his son?
Huh...
A miracle the little bastard survived this long!
We know the story!
The Navy executed every person they could find who was connected to Roger in any way!
But I always thought his father was Dragon!
That's Luffy's father, right? And their brothers!
Yeah, that's what I thought too!
What's the deal here? Does Luffy know about this and he never told anyone?
Garp!
Come here!
You're never gonna believe this!
But I've got a baby on the way!
A boy, I bet!
For obvious reasons, I sadly won't be there for the kid's birth.
Why the hell are you telling this to a Navy officer? What are you thinking?
You realize what'll happen? Are you trying to get the mother of your own damn child executed?
I'm telling you so, that doesn't happen!
Ugh!
There's no doubt the government will manage to dig up my whereabouts for the past year.
And when they do, they'll find her and get her!
Would you approve of them punishing a child who hasn't even been born?
Garp!
You and I have tried to kill each other more times than I can count!
That aside, I know you're an honorable man. One that I can trust.
Look after my child.
Why me, you selfish bastard!
Because...
I know that you'll do it.
Keep him safe for me.
Please, Garp.
I don't know. Are you sure this is the island we're looking for?
It's gotta be. There've been a lot of Roger sightings reported here.
They say he wasn't acting like a pirate, but instead, like a man in love.
The Navy's put Roger's era to an end. And we've gotta cut the bloodline to keep it that way.
Check for pregnancy tests. If they happened within 10 months of his capture, I wanna know about it.
Round up any pregnant women.
And kill any suspicious mothers on the spot.
Round up here on the spot.
Or sadly, I have tried to kill each other.
I thought it was okay.
Tell them briefly Maaróms.
The majority of these animals are someone waiting for us until we find them in the back.
Trance can only break these beasts for this, but rather toute my sum they look like and evalоронize them.
Byeкаudor3
Orgs are they a ship?
This month, five were born.
There are several due next month.
Not yet.
Take in married women, too.
The marriage could be a ruse.
You'll get her back when we've cleared her.
No, not yet.
You have to hold on a while longer.
I'm sorry.
Not yet.
No more pregnant women, sir.
It's been ten months since he went to jail.
I don't think Roger sired a child.
So, that really is the end for the King of the Pirates, huh?
Get away!
Your name is Portgustee Rouge, correct?
Correct?
If it's a girl, Anne.
And if it's a boy, Ace.
Those names, he picked them.
So, his name is Goldie Ace.
Our son.
Our little boy.
Duckbucked.
Oh, Ace.
Rouge!
Stay with us!
I'm going to need you to raise this child, Da-Dun.
Oh, hell no!
Whose baby is this?
What? Why?
I said so. Starting today, you're with Da-Dun.
No!
You're staying with her family, and that's the end of it. And be nice to them.
We've both got the blood of criminals flowing through our veins.
That was the only gift those bastards ever gave us.
I took the name Portkas from my mother because I owe her so much.
But I don't owe my father a damned thing.
He can keep his name.
Whitebeard is my only father.
Got it, old man?
Oh, Garp.
Two years ago, you took your mother's maiden name as your own.
And with your exquisite speed and strength, you quickly gained notoriety throughout the world as the underlining captain of the Spade Pirates.
And that's when we put the pieces together.
There was no doubt that Roger's blood had been passed on.
But Whitebeard came to the same realization and got to you before we did.
In order to secure your mantle as the next king of the pirates, he warmly accepted the son of his own rival aboard his ship.
That's not true!
I joined my father's crew in order to make him the next king!
Nobody believes that, except you.
Why do you think it took us so long to finally catch you?
You were under Whitebeard's protection.
So today, we know that if you were to go free, you'd use your abilities to become the next king.
The only recourse we have to avoid this inevitable risk is to execute you.
Even if it means we face the prospect of war with Whitebeard!
We have a situation! Fleet Admiral! The Gate of Justice! It's opening without any order from us, sir!
And we can't make contact with the control room!
What did you say?!
Maybe if I give it a good hit!
Sure. Maybe if we not.
Do you really think a punch is going to open it?!
Hey, it worked!
Now that's unexpected!
It's opening! Are they actually letting us in?
But that Navy guy said they were going to leave us on the top curtain to run!
It's not the control room! That's in Marineford!
So who's behind this, then?
Huh?
Keep opening!
Just a little more now!
You will open all the way!
I can feel it! My bones are dancing in total harmony with your whirling gadgets and gears!
We move as one!
Yes! Keep going!
There we go! There we go! One little further!
Hey! Wait! Captain Buggy! Are you...
Almost there!
You're really opening it?!
He's our savior! He's the chosen one!
Buggy! Wait!
Oh, would you stop milking it! This is clearly a trick!
Seriously? Who is opening the gate?
Maybe the universe really does want me to be king of the pirates!
Who cares why? It's open! Let's go!
It's so quiet.
Huh! Yeah, you could cut the tension with a knife, huh?
Huh?
Right! Let's do this!
Oh!
They're here!
Ready battle stations! Now!
They appeared out of nowhere! But how did they get in here?
They appeared out of nowhere!
Why don't they get in here?
It's an entire fleet of pirate ships!
Keep an eye out for Whitebeard. He must be there.
Bohemia Knight Doma, Thunderlord Magai,
The DeKalvin Brothers,
Whirlspider Squad!
It's worse than we expected! They've got just about every big-time captain from the New World with them!
We've counted 43 ships in total, and there's no sign of Whitebeard or the Commanders,
but every single one of them is a sworn ally of Whitebeard!
Alright, Ace. We're here!
We've got your back, bro!
Listen to those children panic. It's pathetic!
They actually came?
Should we attack?
Not yet. Whitebeard's gotta be around here somewhere.
He's planted something big, so keep your eyes on the sea!
Now this is fun! I'm ready for some war!
Now come on, Whitebeard! I'm hungry!
Thanks.
Let's eat this!
Where is he?
You figure it's a surprise attack. Whitebeard is no fool. Oh, don't act like you're so smart
There's a shadow in the middle of the bay
It's just as I feel why didn't we plan for this they got their ships coated to ambushes from underwater
It's whitebeard ship the movie day
Oh
Much to the surprise of the Navy the Moby Dick surfaces in the middle of Marineford on
On the deck stands whitebeard the man who race calls father and his 14 commanders the pirates equals family who share with his determination to stop the execution
On the next one piece the beginning of the war ace and whitebeard's past
I'm gonna be king of the pirates